http://www.paperedwonders.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using this Website. PRIVACY POLICY CONSENTThe Website and its Content is owned by Papered Wonders, Inc. (“Company”, “we”, or “us”). The term “you” refers to the user or viewer of our Website.   Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 1, 2018. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy on the Website at any time without notice. Use of any information or contribution that you provide to us, or which is collected by us on or through our Website or its Content is governed by this Privacy Policy. By using our Website or its Content, you consent to this Privacy Policy, whether or not you have read it. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Website or its Content.SUBMISSION, STORAGE AND SHARING OF PERSONAL DATATo use our Website or its Content, we may seek personal data including your name, e-mail address, street address, city, state, billing information, or other personally identifying information (“Confidential Information”), or you may offer or provide a comment, photo, image, video or any other submission to us when visiting or interacting with our Website and its Content (“Other Information”). By providing such Confidential Information or Other Information to us, you grant us permission to use and store such information.   Your Confidential Information is stored through by us internally or through a data management system. Your Confidential Information will only be accessed by those who help to obtain, manage or store that Information, or who have a legitimate need to know such Confidential Information. There may be an occasion where we may ask for demographic information such as gender or age, but if you choose not to provide such data and information, you may still use the Website and its Content, but you may not be able to use those services where demographic information may be required.CONFIDENTIALITYWe aim to keep the Confidential Information that you share with us confidential. Please note that we may disclose such Confidential Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that: (1) such action is necessary to protect and defend our rights or property or those of our users or licensees, (2) to act as immediately necessary in order to protect the personal safety or rights of our users or the public, or (3) to investigate or respond to any real or perceived violation of this Privacy Policy or of our Disclaimer, Terms and Conditions, or any other terms of use or agreement with us. VIEWING BY OTHERSNote that whenever you voluntarily make your Confidential Information or Other Information available for viewing by others online through this Website or its Content, it may be seen, collected and used by others, and therefore, we cannot be responsible for any unauthorized or improper use of the Confidential Information or Other Information that you voluntarily share.PASSWORDSTo use certain features of the Website or its Content, you may need a username and password. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the username and password, and you are responsible for all activities, whether by you or by others, that occur under your username or password and within your account. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized or improper use of your username or password or any other breach of security. To help protect against unauthorized or improper use, make sure that you log out at the end of each session requiring your username and password.   It is your responsibility to protect your own username and password from disclosure to others. We cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to protect your username, password or account information. If you share your username or password with others, they may be able to obtain access to your personal information at your own risk.   By using our Website and its Content you agree to enter true and accurate information on the Website and its Content. If you enter a bogus email address we have the right to immediately inactivate your account. We will use our best efforts to keep your username and password(s) private and will not otherwise share your password(s) without your consent, except as necessary when the law requires it or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary, particularly when disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to others or interfering with our rights or property. UNSUBSCRIBEYou may unsubscribe to our e-newsletters or updates at any time through the unsubscribe link at the footer of all e-mail communications.We manage e-mail lists through a list management system. Unsubscribing from one list managed by us will not necessarily remove you from all publication email lists. If you have questions or are experiencing problems unsubscribing, please contact us at hello@carrylovedesigns.com ANTI-SPAM POLICYWe have a no spam policy and provide you with the ability to opt-out of our communications by selecting the unsubscribe link at the footer of all e-mails. We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information. We will not sell, rent or share your email address. CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCEWe do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age in compliance with COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), and our Website and its Content is directed to individuals who are at least 13 years old or older.ANONYMOUS DATA COLLECTION AND USETo maintain our Website’s high quality, we may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Website by identifying which areas of the Website are most heavily used, and to display content according to your preferences. Your IP address is the number assigned to computers connected to the Internet. This is essentially “traffic data” which cannot personally identify you, but is helpful to us for marketing purposes and for improving our services. Traffic data collection does not follow a user’s activities on any other Websites in any way. Anonymous traffic data may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate basis.SECURITYWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.USE OF “COOKIES”  We may use the standard “cookies” feature of major web browsers. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor do we employ any data-capture mechanisms on our Website other than cookies. You may choose to disable cookies through your own web browser’s settings. However, disabling this function may diminish your experience on the Website and some features may not work as intended. We have no access to or control over any information collected by other individuals, companies or entities whose website or materials may be linked to our Website or its Content.PRIVACY POLICIES OF OTHER WEBSITESWe have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of any other individual, company or entity whose website or materials may be linked to our Website or its Content, and thus we cannot be held liable for the privacy of the information on their website or that you voluntarily share with their website. Please review their privacy policies for guidelines as to how they respectively store, use and protect the privacy of your Confidential Information and Other Information.ASSIGNMENT OF RIGHTSIn the event of an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer of some or all of our assets, you agree we can assign, sell, license or transfer any information that you have provided to us. Please note, however, that any purchasing party is prohibited from using the Confidential Information or Other Information submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy without your prior consent.NOTIFICATION OF CHANGESWe may use your contact information to inform you of changes to the Website or its Content, or, if requested, to send you additional information about us. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter our Website, its Content and this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes and/or modifications shall become effective immediately upon posting our updated Privacy Policy. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically. Continued use of any of information obtained through or on the Website or its Content following the posting of changes and/or modifications constitutes acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at hello@paperedwonders.com
